MAHMUDUL HASAN

Email: hasanmahmudul356@gmail.com

Cell: 01788-208626

Objective

I am looking forward to joining a progressive organization. I am Strong Developer and leader. I have a high level of personal morals and integrity. I am Goal oriented, self-motivated and committed to the successful outcome of the project. I am willing to work hard and have a great desire to learn.

Summary

- Since Now, I have 3+ years plus of extensive hands on experience of website development and Web Application Development.
- An experienced team led Development with excellent communication and interpersonal skills that has the ability to work independently under pressure.
- Currently working as a Programmer at TMSS-ICT.

Skills

Languages/WebDevelopment	PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, MySQL
Frameworks	Laravel, Codelgniter, AJAX, Vue Js, AngularJS
Development Technology	Api, Single Page Application (SPA)
CMS	WordPress.
Databases	MySQL
Tools	PhpStorm , Sublime Text 3, VS Code
Version Control(Git)	Github, Gitlab, Bitbucket
Development Sequence Board	Trello

Experience

TMSS-ICT, HQ kazipara, Dhaka

Programmer (March 2019 - Current)

Responsibilities include New Application development and Fix Issue on Existing Applications.

Remote job, Saudi Arabia

Web Application Developer (July 2018 – May 2019) Responsibilities include New Application development and Fix Issue on Existing Applications

Redsoft Limited, Mouchak, Dhaka

Senior Programmer (October 2017 - April 2018)

Responsibilities include team Lead, direct client communication and software development.

Pacific Group, Gulsan-01, Dhaka

Web Developer (December 2016 - September 2017) Responsibilities include Web Site development.



Projects

Online News Portal Management (CMS)

- Role : Developer
- Tools: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Ajax, jQuery, Vue.js.
- Application Language : English, Bangla
- Url: http://voiceofchandpur.net

Water Company Management Application

- Role : Developer
- Tools: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Ajax, jQuery, Vue.js.
- Application Language: English, Bangla.
- Url: http://shitolpani.com

Accountant application

- * Role : Developer
- Tools: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Ajax, jQuery, Vue.js.
- Application Language : English, Arabic.
- Url: http://account.hawsab.me/en

Dynamic Website Development:

- Role : Developer
- ❖ Tools: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Ajax, jQuery, Vue.js.
- Application Language : English, Arabic.
- Language: Arabic, English
- Url: http://jilani.com.sa, http://jilani.com.sa, http://jilani.com.sa, http://jilani.com.sa, http://jilani.com.sa/

Internal Company Management OR HRM

- Role: Developer
- Tools: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Ajax, jQuery.
- Application Language : English.
- User: Admin, Marketing, Account, HR
- Url: http://www.cellvisiongroup.com/myadmin

Printing Press Management System Software

- Role : Developer
- Tools: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Ajax, jQuery.
- Application Language : English.
- Url: http://www.print.cellvisiongroup.com/

E-paper Application

- Role : Developer
- Tools: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Ajax, jQuery.
- Url: http://amaderorthoneeti.com/epaper

Training Center Management Software

Role : Developer

- ❖ Tools: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Ajax, jQuery.
- ♦ Application Language : English.
- Users : Admin, Teacher, Account, Student.

BulkSMS Application

- Role : Developer
- Tools: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Ajax, jQuery.
- ❖ Application Language : English

Point Of Sale Software.

- Role : Developer
- ❖ Tools: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Ajax, jQuery.
- Application Language : English.

Education

Green University Of Bangladesh, Begum Rokeya Sarani, Dhaka

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering (Studying 10th Semester)

Year: 2018

Mosjid Mission Academy School And College Rajshahi , Rajshahi

Higher School Certificate (HSC)

Year: 2014

Paranpur Kamil Madrasha, Manda, Naogaon

Secondary School Certificate (SSC)

Year: 2012

Professional Training

Dhaka University (IIT)

Web-Design (HTML, CSS, Java Script)

Year: 2015 (4 month)

Creative IT Institute

Web-Design (HTML, CSS, Java Script, Bootstrap, Jquery, PHP, Wordpress)

Year: 2016 (5 month)

Belancer Training Center(LICT)

Web-Development (PHP, Laravel, MySQL)

Year: 2016 (4 month)

Interests

Web Programming

References

References can be provided on request.